I'm sitting at my nail table, which
means we're going to save
these claws now.
I'm going to do this with full cover tips now
because I'm lazy and since I
can never remember what
my actual size is, we'll measure it again
.  Like every two
weeks.  Too small.  The sixth B fits
5.5 B there.  And so that I don't have to roughen up the tips
, I can do this now.
Now the good machine is unpacked
and the nails are roughened.
After roughening the surface, the cuticle must of course also
be removed.
I do that with a cuticle
nipper.  Be careful.
Then you add the hydrator and primer,
and off you go.
Now this little helper comes into
play.  This is a portable
blue light.  Also Vicht.  Guys, I've drastically
improved my nail game in the last few months or years
.  I don't think you guys even realize that
.  You can't either, because I
think I have
n't shown how I
do my nails in over a year or so, which is a shame.  I'm sorry
I let you down
.  I'm back.
Let's get started with the tip.  I do that
with a peel-off gel.  First
a thin layer is applied to the nail, then
to the fake nail.  This is then
carefully combined and placed inside
the lamp.  The nails are on.
I used a bit too much gel, but
we'll ignore that for now.  It needs to be
roughened up again, but before that, it goes
into the large lamp.
And now we finally come to the
fun part: painting.  I don't
have a really cool color to paint
my nails before I do a French manicure
.  That's why I
always mix it
together from about 1000 colors.  First I
mixed two colors together, and then I
painted over another pinkish color, and something
pretty cool usually comes out of that.  That will need
a little more refinement, because
I haven't done that yet and
reduced the size.  I have to
choose between two colors right now.  I
think I'll take that one.  There was
music.  Let's do a two-tone French manicure.
I don't know the other color yet
.  But I'll start anyway
.  This is by far the
hardest part, guys.  French painting
always makes me incredibly
aggressive.  I always do the
outline first, so the border of the
French manicure, and then I fill it in.  I
do all of this with such a tiny little
brush, because otherwise it's
absolutely impossible.  Luckily, I have
a white fineliner pen, so I
drew another line underneath it.
Guys, I don't
think I've ever concentrated like this before, but it turned out
really well.  I was very proud
of myself.  Then, of course,
a brilliant top code is added, and we
're done.  I have to do the whole thing again now
because I was too lazy
to do it directly on both hands.
We won't talk about that, but I'll show you
briefly now.   Does
n't it look so cool?  I'm going to do
the other hand now, just
to motivate myself to keep doing this
.  Stay tuned for a moment.  Thank you very much.   Yes
.